<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Meals That Heals</string>

	<!--<string name="header_web_front_ent">Web Front End</string>-->
    <!--<string name="header_back_end">Back End</string>-->
    <!--<string name="header_mobile">Mobile</string>-->

    <string name="drawer_open">Open</string>
    <string name="drawer_close">Close</string>

    <string name="asthma">Asthma</string>
    <string name="burns">Burns</string>
    <string name="catarrh">Catarrh</string>
    <string name="constipation">Constipation</string>
    <string name="ear">Ear Disease</string>
    <string name="eczema">Eczema</string>
    <string name="eye">Eye</string>
    <string name="hair">Hair Loss</string>
    <string name="hepatitis">Hepatitis</string>
    <string name="ibh">Body Heat</string>
    <string name="jaundice">Jaundice</string>
    <string name="laryngitis">Laryngitis</string>
    <string name="lobido">Low Libido</string>
    <string name="loosemotion">Loose Motion</string>
    <string name="lsc">Low Sperm Count</string>
    <string name="Diabetes">Diabetes</string>
    <string name="malaria">Malaria</string>
    <string name="mouthodour">Mouth Odour</string>
    <string name="pile">Pile</string>
    <string name="poison">Poison</string>
	<string name="ringworm">Ringworm</string>
	<string name="tubaculosis">Tuberculosis</string>
    <string name="typhoid">Typhoid</string>
    <string name="ulcer">Stomach Ulcer</string>
    <string name="weakerrection">Weak Erection</string>
    <string name="whitlow">Whitlow</string>
    <string name="worm">Worms</string>
    <string name="waterretention">Water Retention</string>
    <string name="yellowfever">Diarrhea</string>
	<string name="SkinCare">Ageing</string>
	<string name="herb">HERB</string>
	<string name="cure">CURE</string>


	<string name="pineapple">
		Pineapples’ nutritional benefits are as fascinating as their anatomy.
		Pineapples contain high amounts of vitamin C and manganese.
		And their health and medicinal benefits include their ability to
		improve respiratory health, cure coughs and colds, improve
		digestion, help you lose weight, strengthen bones, improve oral health, etc.
	</string>

	<string name="pepper">
		Peppers have a lot going for them. Low in calories and are loaded with good nutrition.
		All varieties are excellent sources of vitamins A and C, potassium, folic acid, and fiber.
		A chemical compound in pepper called piperine may
		be able to help prevent a breast cancer tumor from developing.
		Red peppers contain more than 200 percent of your daily vitamin C intake.
	</string>

	<string name="honey">
		The benefits of honey go beyond its great taste.
		A great natural source of carbohydrates which provide
		strength and energy to our bodies.honey possesses
		carcinogen-preventing and anti-tumour properties!
		Thanks to its antimicrobial properties, honey not only
		soothes throats but can also kill certain bacteria that causes the infection.
	</string>

	<string name="corn_silk">
		The long shiny fibers at the top of an ear of corn are called corn silk.
		Corn silk contains stigmasterol and sitosterol,
		which are highly effective in preventing heart disease and high cholesterol.
		It also has plant acids that help in improving oral and skin conditions
		as well as regulating glucose levels in your body.
	</string>

	<string name="activated_coal">
		Activated charcoal is a potent natural treatment used to trap toxins and chemicals in the body,
		allowing them to be flushed out so the body doesn’t
		reabsorb them. It’s made from a variety of sources, but when used for natural healing,
		it’s important to select activated charcoal made from coconut shells or other natural sources.
		Activated charcoal is jet black in colour-- odourless, tasteless and non-toxic.
	</string>

	<string name="lime">
		The health benefits of lime include weight loss, skin care,
		improved digestion, relief from constipation, eye care,
		and treatment of scurvy, piles, peptic ulcer, respiratory
		disorders, gout, gums, urinary disorders, etc.
		Limes also contain antioxidants, including flavonol glycosides-containing kaempferol,
		which research has shown stops cell division in several cancers.
	</string>

	<string name="snail_slime">
		Snail Slime is packed with nutrients such as hyaluronic acid,
		glycoprotein, proteoglycans, and antimicrobial and copper peptides,
		all of which are commonly used in beauty products and proven to be beneficial for the skin.
		These elements help to protect the snail’s skin from damage, infection, dryness and UV rays.
	</string>

	<string name="pawpaw">
		The antioxidant zeaxanthin, found in papaya,
		filters out harmful blue light rays and is thought
		to play a protective role in eye health and possibly
		ward off damage from macular degeneration.
		Consumption of the powerful antioxidant beta-carotene (found in papayas) has been
		shown to have an inverse association with the development of colon cancer in the Japanese population.
	</string>

	<string name="cinnamon">
		Cinnamon is a spice that is made from the inner bark of trees called Cinnamomum.
		It is high in a substance called cinnamaldehyde, which is responsible for most of the health benefits.
		Antioxidants protect the body from oxidative damage caused by free radicals.
		Cinnamon is loaded with powerful antioxidants, such as polyphenols (3, 4, 5).
	</string>

	<string name="bitter_kola">
		Bitter kola is a type of nut mostly found in several parts of Nigeria
		and West-Central Africa as a whole and the tree grows in the (tropical) rain forests.
		Its biological name is “Garcinia kola” and belongs to the family of “Guittiferal”.
		Chewing bitter kola relieves coughs, hoarseness, bronchial and throat troubles.
	</string>

	<string name="tomato">
		Tomatoes are widely known for their outstanding antioxidant content,
		including, of course, their oftentimes-rich concentration of lycopene.
		Intake of tomatoes has long been linked to heart health. Fresh tomatoes
		and tomato extracts have been shown to help lower total cholesterol, LDL cholesterol, and triglycerides.
		Tomatoes provide an excellent amount of vitamin C and beta-carotene.
	</string>

	<string name="orange">
		Juicy and sweet and renowned for its concentration of vitamin C,
		oranges make the perfect snack and add a special tang to many recipes;
		it is no wonder that they are one of the most popular fruits in the world.
		the healing properties of oranges have been
		associated with a wide variety of phytonutrient compounds.
	</string>

	<string name="guava">
		Besides its unique flavour and fragrance, guava has been
		hailed as one of the super fruits due to the numerous health benefits it offers.
		It indeed is a powerhouse of nutrients. “This humble fruit is extraordinarily rich in vitamin C,
		lycopene and antioxidants that are beneficial for skin. Guavas are also rich in manganese which helps the body
		to absorb other key nutrients from the food that we eat. Guavas contain folate, a mineral which helps promote fertility.
	</string>

	<string name="carrot">
		The health benefits of carrots include reduced cholesterol, prevention from heart attacks,
		warding off of certain cancers, improving vision, and reducing the signs of premature aging.
		Most of the benefits of carrots can be attributed to their beta-carotene and fiber content.
		This root vegetable is also a good source of antioxidant agents. Furthermore, carrots
		are rich in vitamin A, Vitamin C, Vitamin K, vitamin B8, pantothenic acid, folate,
		potassium, iron, copper, and manganese. Carrots contain just 44 calories per 100gm.
	</string>

	<string name="cucumber">
		Cucumbers belong to the same plant family as squash, pumpkin, and watermelon
		Cucumbers contain an anti-inflammatory flavonol called
		fisetin that appears to play an important role in brain health.
		In addition to improving your memory and protecting your nerve cells from age-related decline,
		fisetin has been found to prevent progressive
		memory and learning impairments in mice with Alzheimer\'s disease.
	</string>

	<string name="onions">
		Onions, like garlic, are members of the Allium family,
		The regular consumption of onions have been
		shown to lower the blood sugar levels. A study found that,
		onions contain allyl propyl disulfide that helps
		to reduce the glucose levels by increasing the amount of insulin.
		onions are also a standout source of quercetin.
	</string>

	<string name="unriped_plantain">
		That unripe plantain you held back, waiting for it to ripe is loaded
		with abundant essential minerals and vitamins such as dietary fibre, iron,
		potassium, vitamin B-complex, magnesium, manganese, copper, niacin, riboflavin and thiamin.
		Various studies conducted have shown that unripe plantain
		contains phytochemical properties such as leucocyanidin which can prevents ulcer.
	</string>

	<string name="lemon">
		The health benefits of lemon include treatment of throat infections,
		indigestion, constipation, dental problems, and fever, internal bleeding,
		rheumatism, burns, obesity, respiratory disorders, cholera and high blood pressure.
		The health benefits of lemons are due to its many nourishing elements like vitamin C,
		vitamin B6, vitamin A, vitamin E, folate, niacin thiamin, riboflavin,
		pantothenic acid, copper,  calcium, iron,  magnesium, potassium, zinc, phosphorus and protein.
	</string>

	<string name="olive_oil">
		Olive oil is a fat obtained from the fruit of the Olea europaea (olive tree).
		Olive oil, rich in monounsaturated fatty acids, is a major component of the Mediterranean diet.
		Monounsaturated fatty acids (MUFAs) are considered a
		healthy dietary fat, as opposed to saturated fats and trans fats.
	</string>

	<string name="mango">
		The mango is a member of the drupe family, a type of plant food in which an outer fleshy part surrounds a shell
		(what we sometimes call a pit) with a seed inside. Olives, dates and coconuts are also types of drupes.
		Mangoes may very well be the king of all fruits. They fight cancer, alkalize the body, aid in weight loss,
		regulate diabetes, help digestion, clean your skin, and make the perfect snack.
	</string>

	<string name="basil_leaf">
		Basil (Ocimum basilicum), also known as Saint Joseph\'s Wort, is an herb belonging to the mint family - Lamiaceae.
		Basil contains high quantities of (E)-beta-caryophyllene (BCP), which may be useful in treating arthritis
		and inflammatory bowel diseases, according to research conducted at the Swiss Federal Institute of Technology.
	</string>

	<string name="milk_weed">
		Milkweeds secrete latex containing cardiac glycosides
		that are medicinally valuable in the treatment of heart disease.
		This same latex is an old home remedy for warts.
	</string>

	<string name="castor_bean">
		 The castor oil plant produces castor beans, which is where the oil cis taken from.
		Castor oil has a multitude of uses, in both the health and industrial sectors.
		The castor bean is composed of 40 percent to 60 percent oil, and this oil is rich in triglycerides known as ricinolein.
	</string>

	<string name="ginger">
		Of the 115 different chemical components found
		in ginger root, the therapeutic benefits come from gingerols,
		the oily resin from the root that acts as a highly potent antioxidant
		and anti-inflammatory agent. These bioactive ingredients, especially [6]-gingerol,
		have been thoroughly evaluated clinically, and the research backs up why you should use ginger on a regular basis
	</string>

	<string name="banana">
		Bananas are good for the heart. They are packed with potassium, a mineral electrolyte that keeps electricity
		flowing throughout your body, which is required to keep
		your heart beating. Bananas\' high potassium and low sodium content may also help
		protect your cardiovascular system against high blood pressure, according to the FDA.
	</string>

	<string name="garlic">
		Garlic is a plant in the Allium (onion) family.
		Two sulfur containing constituents in garlic, diallyl sulfide (DAS) and thiacremonone,
		have anti-arthritic properties. Garlic has also been shown
		to improve inflammatory conditions when referring to allergic airway inflammation.
	</string>
	<string name="search_hint">Search</string>
	<string name="share">Share</string>
	<string name="about">ABOUT</string>
	<string name="version">version 1.0.0</string>

	<string name="www.emfitech.com">www.emfitech.com</string>
	<string name="copyright">&#169; 2016 EMFI-TECH INC.</string>
	<string name="all_rights">All Rights Reserved</string>
	<string name="shared_via"><![CDATA["https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=mealsthatheals.emfitech.com]]>
		Check Out the latest and best natural home cure app for treatment/prevention of ailments and sicknesses through herbs and fruits
	</string>
	<string name="anti_ageing">
		<![CDATA[
				<p>Snail Slime (sticky fluid from snails)is the perfect thing if you want to slow down the ageing process to a snail’s pace.\n</p>"
                " <p> Slime harvested from the creatures is the key ingredient in new range of anti-ageing products.
                </p>
                " <p> The products contain a cocktail of proteins, antioxidants and hyaluronic acid which removes dead cells, reduces inflammation and helps skin retain moisture.
                "<br/><br/>The benefits for human skin were discovered by Chilean snail farmers who noticed their skin healed quickly without scarring when they handled the creatures which were being exported to France."</p>"
                ]]></string>

	<string name="asthmaAbout">
		 <![CDATA[
		 <p>Asthma is a chronic disease involving the airways in the lungs. These airways, or bronchial tubes, allow air to come in and out of the lungs.<br/><br/>
                "If you have asthma your airways are always inflamed. They become even more swollen and the muscles around the airways can tighten when something triggers your symptoms.<br/><br/>"
                " This makes it difficult for air to move in and out of the lungs, causing symptoms such as coughing, wheezing, shortness of breath and/or chest tightness.</p>
                ]]>
	</string>

	<string name="aboutBurns">
		 <![CDATA[
		        "Burns are damage to the skin from heat, fire, radiation, sunlight, electricity or chemicals. There are three degrees of severity:"
                "<br/>"
                "<br/>"
                " <p>&#9827; First-degree: these are the least serious burns. They are marked by redness, and extend only into the outermost layer of skin, known as the epidermis.\n"
                "<br/>"
                "<br/>"
                " &#9827; Second-degree: These extend into skin tissue directly below the epidermis (known as the superficial or papillary dermis) and can involve superficial blistering.\n"
                "<br/>"
                "<br/>"
                "&#9827; Third-degree: These damage all layers of skin. If they cover a large proportion of the body, they can be life-threatening.</p>"
                "<br/>"
                ]]>
	</string>

	<string name="aboutCatarrh">
		<![CDATA[
		 "<p> Catarrh is a build-up of mucus in an airway or cavity of the body.<br/>"
                "It usually affects the back of the nose, the throat or the sinuses (air-filled cavities in the bones of the face).<br/>"
                "It's often temporary, but some people experience it for months or years. This is known as chronic catarrh.<br/>"
                "Catarrh can be a nuisance and may be difficult to get rid of, but it's not harmful and there are treatments available. </p>"
                ]]>
	</string>

	<string name="aboutConstipation">
		<![CDATA[
		"<p>Constipation is a condition of the digestive system. The sufferer has hard feces that are difficult to expel. In most cases, this occurs because the colon
		         has absorbed too much of the water from the food that is in the colon.<br/><br/>"
                "The slower the food moves through your digestive tract, the more water the colon will absorb from food. Consequently, the feces become dry and hard.<br/><br/> "
                "Defecation (emptying the bowels) can become very painful, and in some serious cases there may be symptoms of bowel obstruction. "
                "When the constipation is very severe; when the constipation prevents the passage of feces and gas, it is called obstipation. </p>"
		]]>
	</string>

	<string name="aboutDiabetes">
		<![CDATA[
		"<p> Diabetes, often referred to by doctors as diabetes mellitus, "
                "describes a group of metabolic diseases in which the person has high blood glucose (blood sugar), "
                "either because insulin production is inadequate, or because the body's cells do not respond properly to insulin, or both. "
                "Patients with high blood sugar will typically experience polyuria (frequent urination), "
                "they will become increasingly thirsty (polydipsia) and hungry (polyphagia).</p>"

                " <p> Diabetes, also called diabetes mellitus, has become a very common heath problem. "
                "There are two main types of diabetes- type 1 diabetes in which the body does not produce insulin "
                "and type 2 diabetes in which the body does not produce enough insulin or the insulin that is produced does not work properly.</p>"

                "<p>Some of the common symptoms of diabetes include fatigue, weight loss (even though you are eating more), "
                "excessive thirst, increased urination, cut and bruises that are slow to heal and blurred vision.
                "While there is no cure for diabetes, with your blood sugar level under control you can live a totally normal life. "
                "There are various natural remedies for diabetes that will help you control your blood sugar level.</p>"
                ]]>
	</string>

	<string name="aboutEarDisease">
		<![CDATA[
		        "<p>Ear is the most sensitive part of human body which is responsible to convey us the speech of the world. "
                "A little discomfort to your ear can cause major problems. "
                "The most common problems to the ear are ear infections.<br/><br/>"
                " Such infections damage your middle ear the most and are caused by bacteria and viruses from the environment."
                " Middle ear is the section of the ear which is behind the eardrum and is considered as the most sensitive section."
                " Children are more likely to be affected from such infections the most and these are painful for them.<br/><br/> "
                "If not taken care of these infections can not only be painful but can damage your hearing as well."
                " These infections in ear create irritation in the ear, swelling of ear sections and build up extra fluid in ear.</p>"
                ]]>
	</string>

	     <string name="aboutEczema">
			 <![CDATA[
		      "<p>Eczema is a general term for any superficial inflammatory process involving the epidermis primarily,"
                " marked early by redness, itching, minute papules and vesicles,"
                " weeping, oozing and crusting, and later by scaling, lichenification and often pigmentation."
                " It is also used specifically to refer to the condition atopic dermatitis. </p>"
                ]]>
	</string>

	<string name="aboutEye">
		<![CDATA[
		"<p><b>Cataracts</b></p><p>A cataract is a clouding of the lens of the eye that can make it harder for you to see.</p>"
                " <p><b> Causes of Cataracts</b> </p>"
                " <p> Cataracts happen when protein builds up in the lens of your eye, making it cloudy. "
                "This prevents light from passing clearly through the lens, causing some loss of vision."
                " New lens cells form on the outside of the lens, "
                "and the older cells are compacted into the center of the lens, forming the cataract.</p>"
                "<p><b>Dry Eyes</b></p>"
                "<p>The eye depends on the flow of tears to provide constant moisture and lubrication to maintain vision and comfort."
                " Tears are a combination of water, for moisture; oils, for lubrication; mucus, for even spreading; "
                "and antibodies and special proteins, for resistance to infection."
                " These components are secreted by special glands located around the eye. "
                "When there is an imbalance in this tear system, a person may experience <b>dry eyes</b>.</p>"
                ]]>
	</string>

	<string name="aboutHairLoss">
		<![CDATA[
		        "<p>Hair loss, or alopecia, is a concern for men, women, and children.</p>"
                " <p>Several health conditions, including thyroid disease and iron deficiency
		        anemia, can cause hair loss. While thyroid blood tests and other lab tests, including a complete blood count (CBC), "
                "on people who have ordinary hair loss are usually normal, it is important to exclude treatable causes of hair loss. </p>"
                ]]>
	</string>

	<string name="aboutHepatitis">
		<![CDATA[
		        "<p>Hepatitis is an inflammation of the liver. "
                "The condition can be self-limiting or can progress to fibrosis (scarring), cirrhosis or liver cancer. "
                "Hepatitis viruses are the most common cause of hepatitis in the world but other infections,"
                " toxic substances (e.g. alcohol, certain drugs), and autoimmune diseases can also cause hepatitis. </p>"
                " <p> There are 5 main hepatitis viruses, referred to as types A, B, C, D and E. These 5 types are of greatest concern"
                " because of the burden of illness and death they cause and the potential for outbreaks and epidemic spread."
                " In particular, types B and C lead to chronic disease in hundreds"
                " of millions of people and, together, are the most common cause of liver cirrhosis and cancer.</p>"
                " <p>Hepatitis A and E are typically caused by ingestion of contaminated food or water. "
                "Hepatitis B, C and D usually occur as a result of parenteral contact with infected body fluids. "
                "Common modes of transmission for these viruses include receipt of contaminated blood or blood products, "
                "invasive medical procedures using contaminated equipment and for hepatitis B transmission from mother to baby"
                " at birth, from family member to child, and also by sexual contact.</p>"
                ]]>
	</string>

	<string name="aboutIBH">
		<![CDATA[
		        "<p>Body heat, also known as heat stress, is a common health problem caused by exposure to high temperatures. "
                "It occurs when the body is not able to cool itself enough to keep its temperature within the normal range of 36.5–37.5 degrees Celsius. "
                "The body normally cools off by sweating, but sometimes sweating is not sufficient and the temperature keeps rising.</p>"
                " <p> Factors like very hot and humid weather, spending too much time in the sun, "
                "wearing tight clothing, strenuous workouts or physical exercise and certain medical conditions may cause or worsen the problem. </p>"
                " <p> Body heat is not a disease but it should not be taken lightly. If left untreated, it can develop into a heatstroke. "
                "Anyone can suffer from heat stress, but people over 65, babies and young children,"
                " pregnant and nursing mothers, and people who are physically unwell are at a higher risk. </p>"
		]]>
	</string>

	<string name="aboutJaundice">
		<![CDATA[
		        "<p>Jaundice is not a disease but a sign of an underlying disease. "
                "Alcoholic liver disorder and viral hepatitis are the two most common diseases that result in Jaundice. "
                "Other underlying causes of Jaundice include malaria, cirrhosis, thalassemia, hepatitis A, cholestasis or other disorders of the liver .</p>"
                " <p>Jaundice cannot be treated or better said, treatment of jaundice is usually unnecessary."
                "The correct approach to cure Jaundice is to treat the underlying disease. "
                "Allopathic system prescribes blood test for abnormal red blood cells, bilirubin levels, "
                "hepatitis and substances that indicate liver dysfunction. "
                "Doctor often prescribe additional tests like biopsy or ultrasound to identify the causes of jaundice.</p>"
                " <p> A correct dignosis of underlying cause is vital for taking remedial measures for Jaundice."
                "However certain foods are known to alleviate the symptoms and help improve liver functioning." </p>"
                ]]>
	</string>
<string name="aboutLaryngitis">
	<![CDATA[
	"<p>Laryngitis is the result of an inflammation of the vocal cords (larynx). "
	"It is usually caused by excessive strain on the vocal cords or a viral or bacterial infection.</p>"
	" <p>The most common symptom of laryngitis is a hoarse or weak voice. Sometimes people cannot talk at all. "
	"It is often accompanied by a sore throat and dry cough.</p>"
	" <p> In most cases, it is an acute condition that heals with time and has no serious consequences.  "
	"But you can get rid of the pain and inflammation and restore your voice more quickly with some easy and simple natural remedies.\n"
	"\n"
	"The problem usually lasts for a few days or up to 2 weeks, at the most. "
	"If it persists longer then it is likely to be chronic laryngitis for which you need to consult a doctor.</p>"
	]]>
	</string>

	<string name="aboutLobido">
		<![CDATA[
		       "<p>Libido, colloquially known as sex drive, is a person's overall sexual drive or desire for sexual activity</p>"
                " <p>Low libido describes a decreased interest in sexual activity.\n"
                "\n" "It’s common to lose interest in sex from time to time, and libido levels vary through life. "
                "It’s also normal for your interest not to match your partners at times. "
                "However, low libido for a long period of time may cause concern for some people. "
                "Low libido can sometimes be an indicator of underlying health conditions.</p>"
                " <p>Causes of low libido includes low testosterone, taking certain medications,"
                " Restless Leg Syndrome (RLS), chronic illness, depression, aging etc. </p>"
                ]]>
	</string>

	<string name="aboutLoose_motion">
		<![CDATA[
		         "<p>In simple terms, loose motion means you are having watery stools that occur more frequently than usual. "
                "It is also known as diarrhea, which most people have experienced. It can be acute or chronic.</p>"
                " <p>This common problem occurs when the food and fluids you ingest start passing too quickly or in too large an amount through the colon. </p>"
                " <p> Along with frequent loose, watery stools, you may even have symptoms like abdominal cramps, abdominal pain, a fever, bloating and weakness.\n"
                "To reduce the frequency of loose motion and bring your bowel movements to regularity, there are many simple and easy home remedies.</p>"
                ]]>
	</string>

	<string name="aboutLSC">
		<![CDATA[
		        "<p>This is a situation whereby the number of active cells in the spermatozoa is very low and as a result, "
                "it cannot fertilize the egg in a woman’s ovary that can subsequently lead to "
                "fertilization and eventually pregnancy can occur. When the sperm count of a man is relatively low, "
                "it can lead to infertility, which is inability to bare children. "
                "And this is not healthy for our existence.</p>
		]]>
	</string>

	<string name="aboutMalaria">
		<![CDATA[
		        "<p>Malaria is caused by Plasmodium parasites. "
                "The parasites are transmitted by infected Anopheles mosquitoes, "
                "called ‘malaria vectors’, which bite mainly between dusk and dawn.</p>"
                " <p>Early diagnosis and treatment will help reduce further complications of the disease and prevent deaths.\n"
                "\n" "Depending on the victim’s age, health condition, severity of symptoms, "
                "type of malaria and whether the person is pregnant, the length of treatment and the types of drug will differ</p>"
                " <p>While medicines are the first option to treat malaria, there are a few parasites that can survive in the liver "
                "or are resistant to medicines. And hence it is important to uproot them from the body.</p>"
                ]]>
	</string>

	<string name="aboutMO">
		<![CDATA[
		        "<p>Bad breath or mouth odour (also known as halitosis or malodor) can be very embarrassing and tough on those around you.</p>"
                " <p>Bad breath is often caused by a buildup of bacteria in your mouth that causes inflammation and gives off noxious odours. "
                "When you don’t brush or floss regularly, bacteria accumulate on the bits of food left in your mouth and between your teeth. "
                "The compounds released by these bacteria make your breathe smell.</p>"
                " <p>A number of things can cause mouth odour and they include: dental cavities, gum disease, poor oral hygiene, coated tongue "
                "(a white or yellow coating on the tongue, usually due to inflammation). These are among the most common.</p>";
	]]>
	</string>

	<string name="aboutPile">
		<![CDATA[
		        "<p>Also refered by the name Hemorrhoids, piles are the swollen and itchy varicose veins in the "
                "rectum or anus which is caused by frequent constipations and unclear bowel movement. "
                "It is also caused due to extensive pressure at the veins during pregnancy or delivery.</p>"
                " <p>It has been found that about 70 to 80 percent of adult population worldwide is affected by piles at some point in their life time. "
                "Though piles are not very serious health conditions, they cause itching, uneasiness and bleeding.</p>"
                " <p>Consuming healthy foods and regular exercise are the most effective ways to prevent piles. "
                "But if the condition is severe then surgery is required to remove it.</p>"
                ]]>
	</string>

	<string name="aboutPoison">
		<![CDATA[
		"<p>In biology, poisons are substances that cause disturbances in organisms, "
                "usually by chemical reaction or other activity on the molecular scale, "
                "when an organism absorbs a sufficient quantity.</p>"
                " <p> The fields of medicine (particularly veterinary) and zoology often distinguish a poison from a toxin,and from a venom. "
                "Toxins are poisons produced by organisms in nature, and venoms are toxins injected by a bite or sting (this is exclusive to animals). "
                "The difference between venom and other poisons is the delivery method. Industry, agriculture, "
                "and other sectors use poisons for reasons other than their toxicity. "
                "Pesticides are one group of substances whose toxicity is their prime purpose.</p>"
                " <p> In 2013, 3.3 million cases of unintentional poisonings occurred. "
                "This resulted in 98,000 deaths worldwide, down from 120,000 deaths in 1990 </p>"
                ]]>
	</string>

	<string name="aboutRheumatism">
		<![CDATA[
		"<p>Malaria is an infectious disease often caused by Mycobacterium tuberculosis. </p>"
                " <p> Thick and stubborn mucus in your lungs or sinuses can cause seemingly endless
					spasms of coughing, sneezing and painful infections. In a study published in \"Der Pharma Chemica\" in 2010,
					researchers attempted to find beneficial treatments for patients who have tuberculosis. </p>"
                " <p> As part of their studies, they discovered that a mixture of raw pineapple
					juice, pepper, salt and honey given to patients every day helped to dissolve the mucus in the lungs. </p>"
					]]>
	</string>

	<string name="aboutRingworm">
		<![CDATA[
		"<p>Ringworm (Tinea), as its name appears, isn’t really a worm at all. Ringworm is actually "
                "a type of fungal infection on the outer layer of the skin that appears"
                " like a ring-like circular red rash with dry and flaky edges that often has blisters on them.</p>"
                " <p>Jock itch and Athlete’s foot are its localized forms. Ringworm is extremely itchy and contagious. "
                "It can spread to other parts of body by just touching or coming in contact with a person suffering from ringworm.</p>"
                " <p>Pets like cats and dogs can be one of the main sources of transmitting this infection to humans. "
                "Other ways of transmitting this infection could be through cuts, scratches and wounds. "
                "Ringworm can be easily treated at home without using prescription drugs. "
                "Continue with your treatment for 2-3 weeks, even after getting relief from the symptoms to prevent recurrence.</p>"
                ]]>
	</string>

	<string name="aboutTuba">
		<![CDATA[
		"<p>Tuberculosis is an infectious disease often caused by Mycobacterium tuberculosis. </p>" +
                " <p> Thick and stubborn mucus in your lungs or sinuses can cause seemingly
		endless spasms of coughing, sneezing and painful infections.</p>"
		]]>
	</string>

	<string name="aboutTyphoid">
		<![CDATA[
		       "<p>Typhoid fever, also known as typhoid, is a bacterial infection of the intestinal tract and bloodstream. "
                "It is most commonly caused due to the Salmonella typhi (S. typhi) bacterium.</p>"
                " <p>Once the bacteria enters the body through contaminated food, drinks or water, "
                "they multiply and spread from the intestines into the bloodstream. "
                "The bacteria travel through the blood to your lymph nodes, liver, spleen, gallbladder and other parts of the body.</p>"
                " <p>Early symptoms of typhoid are fever, weakness, headache and abdominal pain. "
                "As the disease gets worse, one can also have symptoms like severe diarrhea, "
                "vomiting, constipation, loss of appetite, skin rashes, blood in the stools, "
                "chills, delirium, hallucinations, fluctuating mood, enlarged liver, nosebleeds and lethargy. "
                "Symptoms usually improve in 2 to 4 weeks with proper treatment.</p>"
                ]]>
	</string>

	<string name="aboutUlcer">
		<![CDATA[
		        "<p>Stomach ulcers are painful sores that can be found in the stomach "
                "lining or small intestine. Stomach ulcers are the most visible sign of peptic ulcer disease."
                " They occur when the thick layer of mucus that protects your stomach from digestive juices is reduced, "
                "Thus enabling the digestive acids to eat away at the lining tissues of the stomach.</p>"
                " <p>There is no clear evidence to suggest that the stress of modern life or a steady diet of fast "
                "food causes ulcers in the stomach and small intestine, but they are nonetheless common in our society</p>"
                " <p>Stomach ulcers are easily cured, but they can become severe without proper treatment.</p>"
		]]>
	</string>

	<string name="aboutWE">
		<![CDATA[
		"<p>When men become sexually aroused, hormones, muscles, nerves, and "
                "blood vessels all work with one another to create an erection. "
                "Nerve signals, sent from the brain to the penis, stimulate muscles to relax. "
                "This, in turn, allows blood to flow to the tissue in the penis. "
                "Once the blood fills the penis and an erection is achieved, "
                "the blood vessels to the penis close off so that the erection is maintained. "
                "Following sexual arousal, the veins to the penis again open up, allowing the blood to leave. </p>"
                " <p>At some point in a man’s life, he may have difficulty achieving or maintaining an erection. "
                "Erection problems occur when you can’t achieve or maintain an erection that’s firm enough to have sexual intercourse. "
                "For most men, this problem occurs occasionally and isn’t a serious issue. "
                "However, if you are unable to achieve an erection one-quarter of the time or more, "
                "you may have a health problem that requires medical attention.</p>"
                " <p>The causes of erection problems can be physical, psychological, or a combination of the two. "
                "Physical causes of erection problems are more common in older men. "
                "They occur because of disorders that can affect the nerves "
                "and blood vessels responsible for causing an erection.</p>"
		]]>
	</string>

	<string name="aboutWhitlow">
		<![CDATA[
		"<p>Whitlow is scientifically called ‘Paronychia’. "
                "This condition is found on the fingers near the nails and is extremely painful and contagious. "
                "The tingling sensation caused due to whitlow in the fingers is extremely bad than pain caused due to severe headache. "
                "This condition is caused in the finger tips due to ‘herpes simplex virus’. "
                "Thus, it is also called ‘Herpetic whitlow’.</p>"
                " <p>Both types of herpes simplex virus – Type 1 and Type 2 can cause herpetic whitlow. "
                "It occurs when the skin is broken on fingertips and it comes directly into contact with the body fluids infected herpes virus.\n"
                "\n"
                "Some symptoms of whitlow include intense pain, itching, swelling or redness on the fingertips. "
                "Small blisters can also be seen. Some general symptoms accompanied with whitlow "
                "include swollen lymph nodes, fever, red streaking on arms. "
                "If these symptoms are seen, it indicates a significant infection.</p>"
                " <p>Though, the problem of whitlow resolves within two to three weeks without treatment. "
                "If you need help from medical practitioner, then he might prescribe you some medications "
                "which can reduce pain and swelling, but if you experience repeated episodes of whitlow, "
                "then he might give you a course of antiviral medication to prevent severe symptoms of its future occurrences.</p>"
		]]>
	</string>

	<string name="aboutWorms">
		<![CDATA[
		"<p>Helminths, also commonly known as parasitic worms, are large multicellular organisms, "
                "which when mature can generally be seen with the naked eye. "
                "They are often referred to as intestinal worms even though not all helminths reside in the intestines; "
                "for example schistosomes are not intestinal worms, but rather reside in blood vessels.</p>"
                "<p>There are several types of worms that can cause problems in humans, "
                "including threadworms, roundworms, tapeworms, whipworms and hookworms.</p>"
                " <p>Intestinal worms can be effectively treated using common modern prescriptions. "
                "These medicines are usually administered in two to three doses, "
                "with a fortnight difference between each consecutive dosage. "
                "However there might be situations where natural cure and home remedies may be equally effective.</p>"
		]]>
	</string>

	<string name="aboutWR">
		<![CDATA[[
		"<p>Water retention, also known as edema, occurs when the lymph system fails to remove excess fluids from "
                "the body and those fluids become trapped and cause swelling in the hands, legs, ankles, and feet. "
                "Edema has many causes, including heart problems, poor circulation, allergies, liver disease, "
                "vitamin deficiencies, kidney problems, and thyroid disorders, among many others. Symptoms of edema vary from person to person, "
                "but typically include weight gain, swelling, itching, aching, bloat, joint stiffness, and high blood pressure.</p>"
                " <p> The key to preventing water retention is to stay hydrated, eat healthy, and "
                "get regular exercise so that your body will function properly and expel excess water naturally. </p>"
		]]>
	</string>

	<string name="cureAntiAgeing">
		<![CDATA[[
		         <p> &#9827; Apply the fluid to directly to your face or allow the snail walk over your face while secreting its fluid
                Don\'t worry, it is totally harmless</p>
		]]>
	</string>

	<string name="cureAsthma">
		<![CDATA[
			"<p> <b>Giant Milkweed (Calotropis Procera)</b></p>"
                "The best natural cure for asthma is the Calotropis Procera."
                "<p>It is commonly called Giant milk weed or Sodom apple. The Yorubas call it bomu bomu, the Hausas named it tumfaa fiyaa,/bam bam bele.
                 It is a fructose shrub and the leaves produce milky juice. Fruits appear like gall."
                " Stem and leaves are whitish green in colour. Leaves arrangement is whorled.
                It is found around homes and garden where humus soil is abundant.
                And the parts used are the leaves and latex. The chemical compounds are calotropin, calotoxin and resinols.
                The smoke from the dried leaves, if inhaled can cure asthma and cough. "
                "Leaves are used to induce breast milk in women and for preparing fresh cow milk called wara (cheese)</p>"
                "<p><b>Procedure</b></p>"
                "For fast and effective results, follow this procedures:<br/>"
                "<br/>"
                "&#9827; The leaves should be washed very well and cooked on medium heat(not more than 10 minutes).<br/>"
                "<br/>"
                "&#9827; Boil with little water, while ensuring the leaves are totally covered with water.<br/>"
                "<br/>"
                "&#9827; The leaves should be arranged in pairs (facing each other) in the water.<br/>"
                "<br/>"
                "&#9827;Half a cup should be taken milkweed times daily morning and night (Should be taken while warm).<br/>"
                "<br/>"
                "&#9827; Take for a minimum of 7 days.";
		]]>
	</string>

	<string name="cureBurns">
		<![CDATA[
			"<p> <b>Manuka Honey</b></p>"
                "The manuka honey is obtained from nectar collected by honey bees from manuka trees found in New Zealand."
                "Honey can be spectacularly effective for severe burns and is the basis of a therapy in China that has attracted much attention from doctors in the West."
                " It is soothing, antiseptic and healing. However, Don't depend on the normal honey from the supermarket – or the health food store – to treat your next burn.
                Instead, try one of the medicinal honeys. The type used in New Zealand research on honey for wound healing is known as manuka honey, and is available commercially. "
                "German physicians have been using Medihoney for treatment of persistent wounds. If you have a really bad burn, be sure to get prompt medical treatment. "
                "<p>Apply the (manuka) honey at the affected area twice (Morning and Night) everyday</p>.";
		]]>
	</string>
	
	<string name="cureCatarrh">
		<![CDATA[
			"<p> <b>Honey and Lime</b></p>"
                "<p>The power of honey to soothe a sore throat and catarrh has long been utilized in traditional and alternative forms of medicine."
                " New research has revealed honey to be as equally effective in suppressing coughs as over-the-counter medications. "
                "Reduced nighttime coughing, catarrh and improved sleep were the results of 2 teaspoons of honey given to children age 2 and older before bedtime."
                " Due to its high vitamin C content, list_item juice offers antioxidants that compliment honey by working to heal underlying issues at the root of the cough.</p>"
                "<p>&clubs; Mix 3 teaspoons of list_item juice into 5 spoons of honey. Take all at once.</p>"
		]]>
	</string>

	<string name="cureConstipation">
		<![CDATA[
			"<p> <b>Basil leaves and Honey</b></p>"
                "Basil leaves (called "Nchuanwu" in Igbo language) and honey is a good combination which keeps your bowel
                clear and help you to overcome constipation. Take some fresh basil leaves and chew them.
                Lick one teaspoon honey and swallow the whole thing followed by a glass of warm water."
                " You will get relief from constipation."
		]]>
	</string>

	<string name="cureDiabetes">
		<![CDATA[
			"<p>Bitter Gourd or Mango Leaf</p>"
                "Bitter gourd, also known as bitter melon or Karela, (Also called \"Ejinrin\" in Yoruba Language), "
                "can be helpful for controlling diabetes due to its blood glucose lowering effects. "
                "It tends to influence the glucose metabolism all over your body rather than a particular organ or tissue."
                "<br/><br/> It helps increase pancreatic insulin secretion and prevents insulin resistance. "
                "Thus, bitter gourd is beneficial for both type 1 and type 2 diabetes. "
                "However, it cannot be used to entirely replace insulin treatment."
                "<p>&#9827; First remove the seeds of two to three bitter gourds and use a juicer to extract the juice.<br/><br/>"
                "&#9827;  Add some water and then drink it on an empty stomach first thing in the morning.<br/><br/>"
                "&#9827; Follow this treatment daily in the morning for at least two months.</p>"
                "<p>The delicate and tender mango leaves can be used to treat diabetes by regulating insulin levels in the blood."
                " They can also help improve blood lipid profiles.</p>"
                "&#9827; Soak 10 to 15 tender mango leaves in a glass of water overnight. "
                "In the morning, filter the water and drink it on an empty stomach.<br/><br/>"
                "&#9827; You can also dry the leaves in the shade and grind them. "
                "Eat one-half teaspoon of powdered mango leaves two times daily."
		]]>
	</string>

	<string name="cureEarDisease">
		<![CDATA[
			"<p> <b>Hot Water, Salt and Honey </b></p>"
                "Mix hot water with a little salt, add honey and stir. Put 2 drops in each ear before going to bed."
		]]>
	</string>

	<string name="cureEczema">
		<![CDATA[
			"<p> <b>Papaya Leaf </b></p>"
                "Papaya leaf juice is the juice extracted from the leaves of papaya plant. "
                "Recent studies have shown that  papaya leaf juice has benefits skin in various ways and enhances the quality and health of your skin."
                "<p>Eczema is effectively treated using papaya leaf juice. <br/>"
                "Take the juice from papaya leaves and use it to apply over the affected areas. "
                "Make sure you scrub your skin well before applying.</p>"
		]]>
	</string>

	<string name="cureEye">
		<![CDATA[
			"<p> <b>Castor Bean Oil</b> </p>"
                "Castor bean oil (Ugba seed in igbo language) is a vegetable oil that is obtained in its purest form from the castor bean seed. "
                "It is tasteless, odourless, and colorless. "
                "The hull of the seed is removed by castor bean cultivators before it is pressed to extract the oil. "
                "Castor oil has a long history. It was widely used in Ancient Egypt and later adopted as a medicine in Persia and China. "
                "It is believed that around 4000 BC, the Ancient Egyptians used it to burn lamps."
                "<p><b>Treats Dry Eyes</b></p>"
                "castor oil is one of the best natural treatments for dry eyes. "
                "For a safe and natural remedy for this condition, you should use castor oil eye drops. "
                "It provides the lubrication that your eyes need to make sure they always stay moist. "
                "Dry eyes can cause other serious eye problems such as keratoconjunctivitissicca, so it is important to treat it as quickly as possible."
                " You will quickly gain relief from the discomfort that comes with this problem."
                "<p><b>Treats Cataracts</b></p>"
                "Castor oil is known to be an effective remedy for dissolving early cataracts. "
                "Experts recommend a drop of this oil in each eye every night before you go to bed. "
                "You should use it before you sleep as the oil clouds vision for a while; hence it’s the safest to use it at night. "
                "Depending on how developed the condition is, cataracts take about 2 to 6 months to disappear. "
                "Remember not to use castor oil that is made for baths or oil packs."
		]]>
	</string>

	<string name="cureHairLoss">
		<![CDATA[
			"<p> <b>Honey and Olive Oil</b> </p>"
                "Honey is thick and the olive oil is quite thin so they balance out each other perfectly and enhance the benefit of each ingredient.<br/><br/>"
                "&#9827; Pour about 5 table spoons of olive oil into a small bowl<br/><br/>"
                "&#9827; Add small drops of honey<br/><br/>"
                "&#9827; whisk constantly and continuing to add honey until the consistency of the mask is smooth, not overly sticky<br/><br/>"
                "&#9827; Massage the mask into damp hair until evenly distributed and fully saturated.<br/><br/>"
                "&#9827; Cover hair with a shower cap, plastic wrap or a plastic grocery bag.<br/><br/>"
                "&#9827; Allow the mask to soak in for 90 minutes<br/><br/>"
                "&#9827; Rinse the mask completely out of the hair and thoroughly with shampoo.<br/><br/>"
                "&#9827; Use this deep conditioning treatment weekly or even twice weekly for dry hair.<br/>"
                "You can also adjust the amount of olive oil and honey according to your hair's needs."
		]]>
	</string>

	<string name="cureHepatitis">
		<![CDATA[
			"<p> <b>Neem Leaves (Dogoyaro)</b> </p>"
                "Neem (Dogoyaro) contains several constituents that have been proved to have anti-viral action; "
                "this makes it useful in treating hepatitis that is viral in origin. "
                "Neem is also said to be capable of destroying the toxins generated in the liver. "
                "The best way to benefit from neem is to make a juice using washed neem leaves; "
                "mix about 30 ml of this juice with half its volume of honey and consume this early every morning on an empty stomach for a week.<br/><br/>"
                "<b>OR</b><br/><br/>"
                "Collect equal quantities of mango, pawpaw and (Neem) dogoyaro leaves, slice a full riped pineapple into the "
                "a pot and boil all with 3 litres of water for 40-45 minutes.<br/>"
                "Drink a full glass thrice daily for one week"
		]]>
	</string>

<string name="cureJaundice">
	<![CDATA[
		"<p> <b>Tomato Juice</b> </p>"
                "One glass of tomato juice, mixed with a pinch of salt and pepper, "
                "taken on empty stomach in the morning is a very effective home cure for jaundice.";
	]]>
</string>

	<string name="cureLaryngitis">
		<![CDATA[
			"<p> <b>Lemon Juice and Salt</b> </p>"
                "The acidic nature of lemon juice can kill bacteria and viruses, and relieve various symptoms of laryngitis."
                " Plus, it helps loosen mucus.<br/> <br/>"
                "&#9827; Squeeze the juice of a lemon into a glass of warm water.<br/>"
                "&#9827; Add one-half teaspoon of sea salt (if you do not have sea salt then just use table salt)<br/>"
                "&#9827; Gargle with this solution several times a day."
		]]>
	</string>

	<string name="cureLibido">
		<![CDATA[
			"<p> <b>Milk and Raw Egg</b> </p>"
                "Nothing about raw eggs sounds sexy, but they are said to arouse your libido. "
                "High in vitamins B5 and B6, eggs also balance hormone levels and fight stress."
                "<p>\"Mother Nature's prescription for a healthy sex life includes high-fat animal foods, "
                "such as whole milk, cream, and butter,\" says Kaayla T. Daniel, "
                "nutritionist and author of The Whole Soy Story: The Dark Side of America's Favorite Health Food."
                " We require plenty of fats, but the natural, "
                "saturated kind (not the trans fats in margarine and grease) in order to produce sex hormones.</p>"
                "<p>Mix 20cl of milk with one raw egg. Stir well and drink 20 mins before intercourse.</p>"
		]]>
	</string>

	<string name="cureLooseMotion">
		<![CDATA[
			"<p> <b>Banana, Lemon and Salt</b> </p>"
                "Both raw and ripe bananas can help treat diarrhea due to their pectin content. "
                "This water-soluble fiber helps absorb fluids in the intestines, which in turn helps add bulk to the stool."
                "<br/>Being high in potassium, it even helps replace electrolytes that may be lost during diarrhea."
                "It can reduce the amount of stool, frequency of vomiting and duration of diarrhea, "
                "as well as reduce the need for oral rehydration solutions or intravenous fluids.\n"
                "A 2012 study published in the Journal of Pharmacognosy and Phytochemistry "
                "also confirms that intake of bananas is beneficial for people suffering from diarrhea."
                "<p>&#9827; When dealing with loose motions, eat a ripe banana every few hours.<br/><br/>"
                "&#9827; Another option is to steam or boil a raw banana, "
                "mash it and then add a little lemon juice and a pinch of salt before eating.</p>"
		]]>
	</string>

	<string name="cureLSC">
		<![CDATA[
			"<p> <b>Guava Leaves, Carrot and Cucumber</b> </p>"
                "To cure low sperm count, you need to get some quantity of guava leaves, "
                "pound and mix with 4 litres of boiled water, allow the water to cool, then "
                "filter it, store the liquid in a clean gallon that has tight cover and put in a "
                "fridge or a cupboard, drink 1 tumbler daily for 2 weeks. After which you should be "
                "eating a mixture of carrot and cucumber every night for another two weeks. The condition will increase drastically."
		]]>
	</string>

	<string name="cureMalaria">
		<![CDATA[
			"<p> <b>Cinnamon, Honey and Pepper</b> </p>"
                "Cinnamon is effective in treating malaria. Add one teaspoon of powdered cinnamon, "
                "a teaspoon of honey, a dash of pepper powder and boil the mixture in a bowl/glass of water. "
                "It can be taken daily and is considered as a valuable remedy for treating the disease."
		]]>
	</string>

	<string name="cureMouthOdour">
		<![CDATA[
			"<p> <b>Honey and Lime</b> </p>"
                "In tackling the problem of mouth odour one can reach out to the sweet golden liquid honey "
                "that is loaded with antibacterial and antifungal properties that have been in use for centuries. "
                "Honey is made up of glucose, fructose, and minerals such as iron, calcium, phosphate, sodium chlorine, potassium, magnesium."
                "<p>&#9827; Wash the limes and cut into two slices<br/><br/>"
                "&#9827; Squeeze the list_item with a juice squeezer or with hands.<br/><br/>"
                "&#9827; Sieve the list_item juice into a container or leave the pulps if you choose to.<br/><br/>"
                "&#9827; Pour in the honey and the mixture together. "
                "Ensure to get an original honey for the to enjoy the numerous benefits.<br/><br/>"
                "&#9827; Wash your mouth twice daily with the mixture(morning and night)<br/><br/></p>"
		]]>
	</string>

	<string name="curePile">
		<![CDATA[
			"<p> <b>Unripe Papaya (Pawpaw)</b> </p>"
                "It has been studied that unripe green papaya or papaya stem contains more papain enzyme than ripe papaya."
                "<p>&#9827; Add unripe papaya in your salad, or chew unripe papaya more frequently"
                " to get rid of piles.<br/><br/>"
		]]>
	</string>

	<string name="curePoison">
		<![CDATA[
			"<p> <b>ACTIVATED COCONUT SHELL CARBON</b> </p>"
                "Activated charcoal is jet black in colour-- odourless, tasteless and non-toxic.In 1813, "
                "an European chemist swallowed five grams of deadly "
                "arsenic trioxide mixed with activated coconut charcoal with no adverse effect."
                "Much later in 1831 , in front of his distinguished colleagues at the French Academy of Medicine, "
                "Professor Touery combined at lethal dose of strychnine with activated charcoal , such was his confidence in this porous carbon. "
                "It absorbs the poison , through the entire length of the stomach and small and large intestines (GI tract)."
                "<p>Activated charcoal keeps the poison from being aBsorbed from the stomach and intestines into the body. Because charcoal is "
                "not \"digested,\" it stays inside the GI tract and eliminates the toxin when the person has a bowel movement."
                "<br/><br/>Activated charcoal powder can adsorb thousands of times its own weight in gases, "
                "heavy metals, poisons, and other chemicals-it renders them ineffective and harmless.The finer the particle size of an activated carbon, "
                "the better the access to the surface area and the faster the rate of adsorption kinetics</p>"
                "<p>&#9827; Get the shell of a coconut.<br/><br/>"
                "&#9827; Burn till it turns into coal.<br/><br/>"
                "&#9827; Take a spoon full mix with water or palm oil and give to poison victim.<br/><br/>"
                "&#9827; <b>Note</b> Activated charcoal powder must be stored in a tightly sealed container, "
                "because it readily adsorbs impurities and moisture from the atmosphere."
		]]>
	</string>

	<string name="cureRingworm">
		<![CDATA[
			"<p> <b>Papaya and Papaya Seed</b> </p>"
                "Raw Papaya is one of the best remedies for treating ring worm. The enzyme contained "
                "in raw papaya is effective in killing the fungus that causes ringworm."
                "<p>&#9827; Take a freshly cut slices of raw papaya and rub gently on the ringworm patches.<br/><br/>"
                "&#9827; Let the enzyme work on the rash for at least 15 minutes and wash off using hot water.<br/><br/>"
                "&#9827; Repeat the process several times a day to get cured completely.<br/><br/>"
                "&#9827; <b>OR</b> Alternatively, make a paste using dried papaya seeds and apply on "
                "the affected area to find quick relief from itching and burning."
		]]>
	</string>

	<string name="cureTub">
		<![CDATA[
			"<p> <b>Pineapple, Pepper, Salt and Honey</b> </p>"
                "In a study published in \"Der Pharma Chemica\" in 2010, researchers attempted to "
                "find beneficial treatments for patients who have tuberculosis."
                "<p> As part of their studies, they discovered that a mixture "
                "of raw pineapple juice, pepper, salt and honey given to patients "
                "every day helped to dissolve the mucus in the lungs."
		]]>
	</string>

	<string name="cureTyphoid">
		<![CDATA[
			"<p> <b>Basil (or Scent) Leaves, Ginger and Honey</b> </p>"
                "Basil is another effective treatment for typhoid fever. "
                "This herb has antibiotic and antibacterial properties that can help get rid of the bacteria that cause typhoid fever. "
                "Moreover, it helps bring down a fever, calm the stomach and boost your immune system."
                "<p>&#9827; Add 20 basil leaves and 1 teaspoon of crushed ginger to 1 cup of water.<br/><br/>"
                "&#9827; Boil it until the solution reduces by half.<br/><br/>"
                "&#9827; Add a little honey and drink this tea 2 or 3 times a day for a few days.<br/><br/>"
                "&#9827; <b>OR</b> Alternatively, You can also extract the juice from 5 to 7 basil leaves. "
                "Add a pinch of freshly ground black pepper to the juice and eat it 2 or 3 times a day for a couple of weeks."
		]]>
	</string>

	<string name="cureUlcer">
		<![CDATA[
			"<p> <b>Unriped Plantain</b> </p>"
                "Unripe plantain has a sticky gum, which is some how hard to remove if it gums on"
                " your hand, so our forefathers, recognized this gum content of an unripe plantain as having the power "
                "to cover up those wound or sore in your intestine, thereby silencing them forever. "
                "<p>&#9827; Get two or three fruits of an unripe plantain, peel out the bark and wash them.<br/><br/>"
                "&#9827; Cut them in smaller pieces, may be 5 mm or so, just cut them in smaller portions, so as to aid its fermentation.<br/><br/>"
                "&#9827; Now, get a 4 or 5-liter plastic container, with cover, and then wash it thoroughly and allow it to dry.<br/><br/>"
                "&#9827; Fill the container with the already pieced unripe plantain.<br/><br/>"
                "&#9827; Now fill the container with clean water, to at least it’s half or more, but don’t fill to the brim.<br/><br/>"
                "&#9827; Cover the container tightly and Shake it together with its contents, and then store "
                "in a good place for fermentation to take place within two or three days.\n<br/><br/>"
                "&#9827; After a period of two to three days, check your concussion, it is now ready for use. "
                "Take half glass morning and night<br/><br/>"
		]]>
	</string>

	<string name="cureWE">
		<![CDATA[
			"<p> <b>Onions or Ginger and Honey</b> </p>"
                "Onion is known as one of the greatest aphrodisiac foods, "
                "it helps increase libido and also strengthens the reproducing organs. "
                "Onions also increase the testosterone levels in the body and can help in increasing the sexual stamina.<br/><br/>"
                "Ginger is a rhizome that is credited with the power to increase blood circulation in the body, "
                "it is only natural that ginger can cure ED.<br/><br/>"
                "<p>&#9827; Get 5 Onions or Ginger, boil and squeeze out the juice.<br/><br/>"
                "&#9827; Mix with the same quantity of honey.<br/><br/>"
                "&#9827; Pour in a clean bottle.<br/><br/>"
                "&#9827; Drink a spoonful after each meal.<br/><br/>"
                "&#9827; <b>OR</b> Take one tablespoon of the Onions/ginger extract every day with a tablespoon of honey and one half boiled egg before bedtime. "
                "Do this for a month to see the tremendous change in sexual performance.<br/><br/>"
		]]>
	</string>

	<string name="cureWhitlow">
		<![CDATA[
			"<p> <b>LEMON</b> </p>"
                "<p>&#9827; Take a lemon and make a hole into it.<br/><br/>"
                "&#9827; Now, insert the affected finger into this hole for about 30 minutes and it "
                "should be done twice daily for quick healing.<br/><br/>"
		]]>
	</string>

	<string name="cureWorms">
		<![CDATA[
			"<p> <b>Papaya Seeds, Leaves and Honey</b> </p>"
                "Papaya seeds are very useful in treating and eliminating intestinal worms. "
                "Caricin which is effective in eliminating roundworms is present in ample quantity in papaya seeds."
                "<p>&#9827; Dry and Powder the seeds.<br/><br/>"
                "&#9827; Add one teaspoon of this powder in a cup of milk or water.<br/><br/>"
                "&#9827; Drink on empty stomach in the morning, daily.<br/><br/>"
                "<p> Papaya leaves are also useful for treating intestinal worms.</p>"
                "&#9827; Make an infusion by taking 15grams of dried Papaya leaves and add about 250ml of boiling water to it.<br/><br/>"
                "&#9827;Add honey to it before drinking<br/><br/>"
                "&#9827;One tablespoon of fresh unripe papaya juice and equal quantity of honey mixed with three tablespoons "
                "of hot water can be taken to treat roundworms. If this is administered to adults, "
                "this should be followed by a dose of 30 to 60ml of castor oil(Ugba seed oil) "
                "mixed in 250ml of lukewarm milk after two hours. For children of seven to ten years of age, "
                "half of the dosage is sufficient and for children below three years, one tablespoon of this dosage is sufficient.<br/><br/>"
		]]>
	</string>

	<string name="cureWR">
		<![CDATA[
			"<p> <b>Corn Silk Tea</b> </p>"
                "Corn silk, the threadlike strands that grow at the end of a corn stalk, "
                "is rich in antioxidants, flavonoids, polyphenols, and vitamin K. "
                "It’s great for treating kidney disorders and urinary infections, and it reduces uric acid and water retention. "
                "As a natural diuretic, it eliminates toxins and waste. In addition to treating edema, it also helps with gout and arthritis. "
                "Consult a doctor before use as it may interact negatively with blood thinners."
                "<p>&#9827; Add ¼ cup fresh corn silk or 2 teaspoons dried corn silk to boiling water.<br/><br/>"
                "&#9827; Cut them in smaller pieces, may be 5 mm or so, just cut them in smaller portions, so as to aid its fermentation.<br/><br/>"
                "&#9827; Remove from heat and let steep 5-10 minutes.<br/><br/>"
                "&#9827; Strain and drink.<br/><br/>"
                "&#9827; Repeat twice daily.<br/><br/>"
		]]>
	</string>

	<string name="cureYellow">
		<![CDATA[
			"<p> <b>Lime Juice and Salt</b> </p>"
                "Lime juice mixed with a pinch of salt is one of the best home remedies for diarrhea.
                 You can drink list_item juice in lukewarm water. "
                "You can also add honey for improved taste and it is a great diarrhea reliever. "
                "It can be consumed 2-3 times a day for the best results."
		]]>
	</string>

	<string name="cureIBH">
		<![CDATA[
			"<p> <b>A young or immature coconut, Honey</b> </p>"
                "&#9827; Lay the young coconut by it sides and cut off slices from the bottom so
                as to find the coconut soft spot or eye (a soft whitish spot).<br/><br/>"
                "&#9827; Stick your knife through the coconut eye and drain the coconut water in mug. It should be a yellowish/clear color."
                "&#9827; Remove the coconut lid with your knife and scoop out the coconut meat with a spoon <br/><br/>"
                "&#9827; Add all ingredients (coconut water, coconut meat and spoons of honey to taste depending on the size and quantity of the coconut)
                         to a high speed blender. Begin blending on a low speed, then switch to high speed.
                         Blend for at least two minutes or till when you can no longer see the pieces of the coconut meat."
                         "&#9827; You may sieve off the unblended  particles <br/><br/>"
                         "&#9827; Keep in fridge afterwards. (A blend will last for at least four days) <br/><br/>"
                         "&#9827; Drink (1/2) half a glass every night. <br/><br/>"
		]]>
	</string>
	<string name="slime">Slime</string>
	<string name="applying_slime">Applying Slime</string>
	<string name="milkweed">Milkweed</string>
	<string name="manuka_plant">Manuka Plant</string>
	<string name="raw_manuka_honey">Raw Manuka Honey</string>
	<string name="honey_title">Honey</string>
	<string name="lime_title">Lime</string>
	<string name="basil_leaves">Basil Leaves</string>
	<string name="bitter_gourd">Bitter Gourd</string>
	<string name="mango_leaves">Mango Leaves</string>
	<string name="salt">Salt</string>
	<string name="warm_water">Warm Water</string>
	<string name="papaya_leaf">Papaya Leaf</string>
	<string name="papaya_leaf_juice">Papaya Leaf Juice</string>
	<string name="castor_seed">Castor Seed</string>
	<string name="castor_oil">Castor Oil</string>
	<string name="castor_bean_seed_and_oil">Castor bean Seed and Oil</string>
	<string name="olive_oil_title">Olive Oil</string>
	<string name="neem_leaves">Neem Leaves</string>
	<string name="pineapple_title">Pineapple</string>
	<string name="watermelon">Watermelon</string>
	<string name="milk">Milk</string>
	<string name="muskmelon">Muskmelon</string>
	<string name="cucumber_title">Cucumber</string>
	<string name="tomato_juice">Tomato Juice</string>
	<string name="pepper_title">Pepper</string>
	<string name="lemon_juice">Lemon Juice</string>
	<string name="raw_egg">Raw Egg</string>
	<string name="banana_title">Banana</string>
	<string name="guava_leaves">Guava Leaves</string>
	<string name="carrot_title">Carrot</string>
	<string name="cinnamon_title">Cinnamon</string>
	<string name="unripe_papapya">Unripe Papapya</string>
	<string name="activated_coal_title">Activated Coal</string>
	<string name="coconut_shell">Coconut Shell</string>
	<string name="burnt_coconut">Burnt Coconut</string>
	<string name="pawpaw_title">Pawpaw</string>
	<string name="dried_papaya_seed">Dried Papaya Seed</string>
	<string name="ginger_title">Ginger</string>
	<string name="black_pepper">Black Pepper</string>
	<string name="unriped_plantain_title">Unriped Plantain</string>
	<string name="onion">Onion</string>
	<string name="soft_boiled_egg">Soft Boiled Egg</string>
	<string name="lemon_title">LEMON</string>
	<string name="papaya_seeds">Papaya Seeds</string>
	<string name="papaya_leaves">Papaya Leaves</string>
	<string name="corn_silk_title">Corn Silk</string>
	<string name="APP_NAME">Homespital</string>
	<string name="DRAWER_OPEN">Open</string>
	<string name="IBH">Body Heat</string>
	<string name="LSC">Low Sperm Count</string>
	<string name="Mango">"\"Mango is a member of the drupe family, a kind of plant foods, in which an outer fleshy part surrounds a shell (what we sometimes call a well) with an internal alL seed. Olive, dates and coconuts are also types of stone fruit. Mango might be the king of all fruits. fight cancer, alkalize the body, L aid in weight loss, regular diabetes, aids digestion, cleanse the skin and make the perfect snack. \" "</string>
	<string name="burn">burn</string>
	<string name="basil">basil</string>
	<string name="young_coconut">Young Coconut</string>
</resources>
